touchtapplay.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Touch Tap Play

Touch, Tap, Play is committed to protecting you and your family’s personal information and privacy when using Touch, Tap, Play’s (the Website) services. This Privacy Policy relates to our use of any personal information you provide through the Touch, Tap, Play website, and/or information that we collect during your visit.

**Collecting your Personal Information**  
If you wish to do so, you can remain anonymous for the entire duration of your visit on the Touch, Tap, Play website. However, we do require personal information from you in a few specific circumstances. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (usually your name and e-mail address). Generally, this information is requested when posting comments on the website, when you are asked to register before entering a contest, if you subscribe to one of our properties or elect to participate in a survey.

You are not obliged to provide a real e-mail address when commenting on your website (but we can’t contact you with an answer if one is required). If you don’t want to provide your real email address, you can use a generic one like: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

When you leave comments on the site, we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. Visitor comments may checked through an automated spam detection service.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

Touch, Tap, Play allows third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements within the Website. These third-party servers or networks use technology to send advertisements, directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

Your visit means you agree with our website using cookies. When it comes to Google advertising, users may opt out of the use of their cookie to receive personalized advertising by visiting [their page](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en).

If you decide to contact us via the contact form on our website, we will collect and store your email address (provided when you contact us), as well as the IP you sent the information from and all the data that you send our way via the contact form itself. We will store the contact form you submit for at most 24 months for customer service purposes and to improve our service, but we will never use that information for marketing purposes.

You need to acknowledge that, whenever you disclose information in public areas on the Website, such as comment areas on the Website, the information in the comment you post becomes public. You should never share personal data (including, but not limited to usernames and passwords) in the public comments you post on our website. We will do our best to remove such information posted on our website, but it is ultimately your responsibility.

We also collect, for statistical and analytics purposes, data from your visit patterns on our website. Information such as pages you have visited, duration of your visit and more are collected during your visit and we use this data to measure the success of our articles, be able to provide you with content that you enjoy and provide our advertising partners with details regarding the reach of this website and number of visitors it receives, including the country or city of origin and some demographic details.

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Using your Personal Information**  
Touch, Tap, Play will use the Personal Information you submit to (1) make sure we credit your work correctly in case of user submitted content; (2) to correctly send you prizes you might win in contests held on the Website; and (3) to contact you with important updates or answers you have requests. However, when you submit User Content, we will only share the name you allow us to share (which can also be a nickname or alias). We will never send you unwanted e-mails, messages or promotional features. We will never share, rent or sell your e-mail address to any other company or third party.

All the stats we collect from tracking your visit to our website are used for better understanding user behavior, provide content our readers are interested in, tracking the performance of specific pages and articles. We also provide generic numbers (visits, pages, duration, locations) to our advertising partners.

**Email Correspondence**  
Touch, Tap, Play staff will respond to e-mails sent directly to them via the contact form or other ways of contact. The sender’s e-mail address will never be shared and we will not use your e-mail address to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail.

**How we protect information collected from you**  
We show great interest in confidentiality. Touch, Tap, Play is a spam free zone. Also, we will never share your Personal Information or e-mail address to third parties without your consent. Any statistics that we might offer to our advertisement networks and partners does not include any personal identifying information about any individual user. We do our best efforts to protect the security of your personal information.

**Notification of Changes**  
We may change the content of our privacy policy, so make sure you check this page regularly.

**Affiliate disclaimer**  
Touch Tap Play is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com. We may also be part of other affiliate programs, earning an amount of money for every purchase you made by following links on our website. However, the price that you pay for the products you get to by following our links is not different from the price you would pay by visiting the same product on the same website directly.

This Privacy Policy has been updated today, 24th of May, 2018.
